ilovedeals.sg 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - iLoveDeals Singapore

ILOVEDEALS PTE LTD (Company Registration Number: 201133342G) or “ILOVEDEALS” (referred to as “us” or “we”) is committed to protecting the privacy of our Users. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the ILOVEDEALS website (collectively, the "Site"). Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the "Users") and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please email us at info@ilovedeals.sg. 

**Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing or using our website, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to all the terms of this Privacy Policy and our website terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms, exit this page and do not access or use the website.**

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**

Personally Identifiable Information is the information that identifies a specific User. 

We will request Users to provide us some personal information when you do the following in our Site 

1\.       1. Creating an account 

2\.       2. Viewing a deal 

3\.       3. Ordering a deal 

4\.       4. Posting review 

5\.       5. Sending us feedback 

6\.       6. Filling out a survey 

7\.       7. Product & service inquiries 

If you are engaging in an identification activity, following personal information may be collected 

1\.       1. First name 

2\.       2. Last name 

3\.       3. Mailing address 

4\.       4. Email address 

5\.       5. Telephone number 

6\.       6. Gender 

7\.       7. Date of birth 

8\.       8. Credit card information 

9\.       9. Bank account information 

It is always your preference to choose to engage any identification activity in our Site. 

We use PII to 

1\.       1. Enhance the operation of the Site 

2\.       2. Enhance Site performance 

3\.       3. Improve our marketing and promotional efforts 

4\.       4. Analyses Users’ trend 

5\.       5. Improve our product and service offerings 

All PII will be utilized in accordance with the relevant privacy law of Singapore. 

**Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information (NPII)**

Non-Personally Identifiable Information is the information that does not identify a specific User. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information can be included following 

1\.       1. URL of the website you visited before coming to our Site 

2\.       2. URL of the website you visit after leaving our Site 

3\.       3. Type of browser you use 

4\.       4. Internet Protocol ("IP") address 

We and our authorized third party service providers and advertisers may collect this information when you visit our Site. 

We use NPII for 

1\.       1. Troubleshooting 

2\.       2. Analyze Users’ trend 

3\.       3. Gather demographic information 

We may also share this information with our authorized third party service providers and advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming. 

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**

We will not share your PII with other parties except as provided below: 

We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers. We provide some of our product and service through third parties. These third party service providers perform functions on our behalf, such as sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your information with the third party service providers for them to send postal or email to Users on our behalf, organize and remove repetitive information on Users list, analyze data for our internal use, provide marketing assistance, provide search results, operate the Site, troubleshooting, and provide any other customer service support. We will only share your PII with a third party service provider that complies with our data protection standard. We may share your information in a Business Transfer. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including PII. 

ILOVEDEALS will exercise its reasonable effort to ensure that the transferred PII will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others. We may also disclose PII when we believe that the disclosure is required to comply with the law or a court order and to enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use or other agreements. 

**Disclosure of Non-Personally Identifiable Information (NPII)**

We may disclose or share NPII with business partners, affiliates and advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any PII) with third party advertising companies. We use third party service providers to collect and analyze NPII relating to the Site and to constantly improve the quality of the Site. We may publish the collected NPII for promotional purposes. 

Updating and Correcting Information 

You need to access to your ILOVEDEALS account to update your PII or you may change any of your PII by sending us an email at info@ilovedeals.sg

Indicate following information when you contact us. 

1\.       1. Name 

2\.       2. Email Address 

3\.       3. Inquires 

**User Choices on Collection and Use of Information**

You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. "Administrative Emails" relate to a User's activity on the Site, and include emails regarding a particular User's account and requests or inquiries. In contrast to Administrative Emails, however, you do have a choice to opt-out of promotional emails. Promotional emails refer to emails that advertise our product and service, and/or the product and service of our advertisers and affiliates. If you do not wish to receive promotional emails from us, you may unsubscribe promotional emails at any time by emailing us at info@ilovedeals.sg or by checking the "unsubscribe" button at the bottom of promotional emails. When contacting us, please indicate your name and email address, and what promotional emails you do not wish to receive. 

**Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites**

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on www.ilovedeals.sg. Other websites that may be accessible through this Site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices that may differ from this Site. If you access any other website through the Site, we urge you to review the website's Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. 

**Security of Information**

We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the PII of our Users. Your ILOVEDEALS account is encrypted. All our Users’ information are stored in our servers located in Singapore. Your sensitive Users’ information (such as credit card information) is encrypted by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your PII is secure. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your PII resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. Regarding information transmitted between the website and and/or Users, while we take reasonable precautions to safeguard this information, we may be unable to prevent unauthorized access to such information by third parties or inadvertent disclosure of such information during transit. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. If you suspect or discover that an unauthorized access has been attempted, please inform ILOVEDEALS immediately at info@ilovedeals.sg. 

**Data Tracking**

For your best Site usage experience, we have store cookies or other tracking devices on your computer. Cookies is a small text file that is stored in a Users’ computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that Users. We use cookies to save your time while using the Site, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect NPII from you, such as pages you visited and the links you clicked on. Use of the information collected by cookies helps us to create a user-friendly Site for Users. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete cookies or other tracking devices, some parts of the Site may not work properly. 

**Other Privacy Issues**

We may provide areas on our Site where you can publicly post information about yourself, can communicate with others such as discussion boards or blogs, or can review products, restaurants, and submit media content. This information may be accessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others. For example, if you post your email address along with a public restaurant review, you may receive unsolicited messages. We have no control over who read your postings or what other Users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use cautiously when posting any personal information. We do obtain consent from our Users to post their name along with their reviews. 

**Changes to this Policy**

ILOVEDEALS will be committed itself in protecting and maximizing our Users' privacy. We will amend the policy from time to time based on the business progression. Users are responsible to review the Privacy Policy changes from time to time. The revised Privacy Policy will be effective immediately after Privacy Policy changes. Your continuous use of the Site after effectiveness of Privacy Policy revisions will constitute your acknowledgement and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of the revised Privacy Policy, you can choose to terminate your Site Users’ account. 

**Contact Us**

Feel free to drop us an email for further inquires 

Customer Service Inquiries: info@ilovedeals.sg
